so what do i need to do
那我需要做什么吗
You should stay in Quanxian Camp
你还是留在泉先大营吧
Go to the enemy camp this time
此次前去敌人军营
The fewer people go, the better
去的人越少越好
What's more, you have the power of the emperor
何况你身负皇天力量
for the white king
为了白王
we can't put you at risk
我们也不能让你涉险
Nasheng, let's rescue Yanxi
那笙 我们去营救炎汐
there's always someone left
总要有一人留下来
Preparing for Yanxi's return
为炎汐回来做准备
so cool
好 那宁凉
You must bring Yan Xi back smoothly.
你一定要把炎汐顺利接回来啊
I will
我会的
Lord, your face
少主 你的脸色
i'm fine
我没事
Then I will contact Xiang to rescue Yanxi.
那我去跟湘联系营救炎汐一事
I'll take care of Bai Ying's sister here.
我在这里照顾白璎姐姐吧
I'll go to Xijing
我去找西京
Go to Taoyuan County later
稍后便前往桃源郡
good
好
Neptune
海皇
Si Shi
肆师
I feel a powerful force
我感觉有一股强大的力量
trying to devour me
正想要吞噬我
Is the backlash getting worse?
是反噬加重了吗
you don't have to force
你不必勉强的
White King's injury is not serious
白王伤势已无大碍
It's only a matter of time before you wake up
苏醒只是时间的问题
What you have to do now is retreat
您现在要做的是闭关疗伤
suppress the backlash
将反噬之力压制住
i will help you
我会助你的
There is a teacher
有劳肆师了
Prince, don't worry
太子哥哥 你放心吧
leave it to me here
这里交给我
I will take good care of Sister Bai Ying
我会照顾好白璎姐姐的
I'm relieved
我放心
Then you must succeed in Taoyuan County.
那你去桃源郡一定要成功啊
Your Highness
殿下
You finally came
你终于来了
What about Sheng, Ying, how are they?
那笙呢 阿璎他们怎么样
It's good, it's Aying
挺好的 就是阿璎
what happened to Aying
阿璎怎么了
She stayed at the Quanxian camp and was healing.
她留在了泉先大营正在疗伤
Fortunately, no life worries
还好没什么性命之忧
Su G in order to heal her
苏摹为了给她疗伤
lost too much mana
损失了太多法力
Recuperating now
现在也在闭关休养
A Ying is in a coma and Su G retreats
阿璎昏迷 苏摹闭关
what to do next
那接下来该怎么办
I'm coming to find you
我过来找你
Just to tell you what's next
就是为了跟你说接下来的事情
That's a good way
这不失为一个好办法
can try
可以一试
Yes
是
Without further ado
事不宜迟
Let's go find this Gao Shunzhao tonight
我们今夜就去找这个高舜昭
ok i will arrange
好 我来安排
His Royal Highness Zhenlan, General Xijing
真岚殿下 西京将军
have not seen you for a long time
好久不见
Taoyuan Village last time
上次桃源村一别
I don't know if everyone is okay
不知大家可否安好
it's good
自是不错
You should know the purpose of our trip
你应该知道我们此行的目的
Cangliu kills people in this battle
沧流此役 杀伤百姓
Taoyuan County after the Battle of the Falcon
桃源郡经过风隼一战之后
badly damaged
元气大伤
Now is the time for everything to be rebuilt
这会儿正是百废待兴之时
Can you show us a clear way?
可否给我们指一条明路啊
Minglu dare not say
明路倒不敢说
We are here to invite you to cooperate with us
我们此行是想让您跟我们合作的
what do you mean
你的意思是
Want us to surrender to Kongsang and Izumi
想让我们臣服于空桑和泉先
become an affiliated county of one of their
成为他们某一方的一个附属郡
if so
如果是这样
and we are now surrendered to the river
和我们现在臣服于沧流
What's the difference
还有什么区别呢
That was not what I meant
我不是这个意思
i mean to say
我的意思是说
Together we create a new
我们共同一起创造一个新的
peaceful cloud
安宁的云荒
Just like we and Izumi
就好像我们和泉先
Air Sea Alliance Between Us
我们之间的空海联盟
by no means a party
绝不是某一方
surrender to the alliance of the other
臣服于另一方的联盟
It's an alliance for the sake of each other's stable lives
而是为了各自安定生活的联盟
I know
我知道
Governor Gao is diligent in politics and loves the people
高总督勤政爱民
The people are great
百姓是大过天的
so do we
我们也一样
Kong Sang hopes that 100,000 people will see the sun again
空桑希望十万子民重见天日
Quan Xian hopes to return to Biluohai
泉先希望能够重归碧落海
We are all for our own people
我们都是为了各自的百姓
to fight for their own peace
去争取各自的安定
Last time I returned to Taoyuan County
上次重回桃源郡
I also want to convince you
心中也是想要说服你
surrender to the lord
臣服于少主的
But I know
但是我知道
You only want the well-being of the people
你一心只想百姓安康
Not someone who is dependent on power
绝不是依附权势之人
From what I know about the young master
凭我对少主的了解
He also disdains power
他也不屑于权力
I just want us to live a happy life
一心只想让我们过上安乐的生活
we all understand each other
我们都是相互理解的
This is the general trend of the people
这是人心所向 大势所趋
It's what you want
也是你心中所愿
Let Taoyuan County become Taoyuan again
让桃源郡重新成为桃源
Yes
是啊
Over the years, I have been fighting hard
这些年沧流穷兵黩武
Will be a good Taoyuan County
将好好的一个桃源郡
turned into ruins
变成了废墟
Huge losses in this battle
经此一役 损失惨重
I'm on pins and needles
我如坐针毡呐
if you can
如果你们能让
people live a peaceful life
百姓过上安定的生活
I will definitely help
我一定会鼎力相助
I will not give up
我不会放弃
Any chance to save the people of Taoyuan County
救助桃源郡百姓的任何机会
Governor Gao, don't worry
高总督 您放心
we won't let you down
我们不会让您失望的
good
好
how to arrange
那如何安排
how do you want to do it
你想怎么做
we need you
我们需要你
Not good, the adult was assassinated.
不好了 大人遇刺了
adult
大人
Taoyuan County Governor's Office Infiltrated Assassin
桃源郡总督府潜入刺客
Gao Shunzhao's life and death unknown
高舜昭遇刺 生死不明
I see
我知道了
what do you think about this
这件事你怎么看
this action
这次行动
It's clearly what Kongsang did.
很明显是空桑所为
The purpose is also clear
目的也很明确
Intended to capture Taoyuan County
意在夺取桃源郡
If Gao Shunzhao has three longs and two shorts
高舜昭若是有个三长两短
they can take the two-headed Garuda Token
他们便可夺取双头金翅鸟令符
then
届时
Taoyuan County can be placed under Kong Sang's command
桃源郡便可归入空桑麾下
Nan Zhao please order
南昭请命
Lead troops to Taoyuan County to quell the rebellion
带兵前往桃源郡平定叛乱
Pingding Taoyuan County
平定桃源郡
I'll send someone
我自会派人去
I want to give you a more important task
我要交给你一个更重要的任务
The young master is in retreat, you two are watching closely
少主在闭关 你俩看紧了
Don't let anyone come near you understand?
不得让任何人靠近 明白吗
Yes Yes
是 是
Ning Liang
宁凉
I guess you're here
我就猜你在这儿
I'm here of course
我自然在这儿
Young Master is in retreat, I can't worry
少主在闭关 我放心不下
don't worry about anything
放心不下什么
You do not understand
你不懂
rightist
右权使
There is news from Taoyuan County
桃源郡那边传来消息
His Royal Highness Zhenlan and General Xijing
真岚殿下和西京将军
Gao Shunzhao has been controlled
已经控制了高舜昭
Successfully caught Cang Liu's attention
成功引起了沧流的注意
you go down
你下去吧
Yes
是
Prince Zhenlan, they succeeded
真岚太子他们成功了
Xiang should also start to act
湘应该也开始行动
What about Yanxi?
那炎汐怎么办啊
Lord, they have already planned
少主他们已经计划好了
I'm going to meet with Xiang
我去和湘会合
no danger
不会出危险的
Then be safe on the road
那 那你们路上注意安全啊
Expedition to Taoyuan County
出征桃源郡
Yes
是
Bai Ying, are you awake?
白璎 你醒了吗
you slept so long
你睡了这么久
Have you had a lot of dreams?
是不是做了很多的梦啊
dreaming
在梦里
I don't know if there will be me
不知道会不会有我
Bai Ying
白璎
Who are you
你是谁
I'll take you out
我来带你出去
who are you and where are you
你是谁 你在哪儿
What's this
这是什么
tears
泪水
tears whose tears
泪水 谁的泪水
those are my tears
那是我的泪水
Why is it in my hands
为什么会在我手上
Because my beloved won't wake up
因为我心爱的人不肯醒来
i'm afraid to lose her
我害怕失去她
Who is your beloved where are you
你心爱的人是谁 你在哪儿
you follow me
你跟着我走
Bai Ying come with me
白璎 跟我来
you're awake
你醒了
Hai Huang, you are over the line
海皇 你逾矩了
Where is this
这是哪儿啊
This is Quanxian Camp
这是泉先大营
you forgot
你忘了
after you are injured
你受伤以后
I'll bring you here to heal
我就带你来这疗伤
Do not you remember
你不记得了吗
I am Su G
我是苏摹
I know you are Su G
我知道你是苏摹
Unless you forcibly open her five rhymes and six sleeps
除非强行打开她的五韵六觉
Re-inject mana
再注入法力
But if it is forced
不过如果这样强行的话
Will cause some damage to the White King
会对白王造成一定伤害的
Is it because of this
难道是因为这样
So Bai Ying is a little alienated from me now
所以白璎现在有些疏远我
Except you remember that I am the emperor of the sea
你除了记得我是海皇
remember what
还记得什么
I remember the Air Sea Alliance
我记得空海联盟
Let's unpack together
我们一起去解封印
Unseal
解封印
what about your highness
殿下呢
he's not here
他不在这儿
where did he go
他去哪儿了
He went to Taoyuan County
他去了桃源郡
will be back soon
很快就会回来
don't worry
你先别着急
Maybe you just woke up
可能是你刚刚醒过来
Confused
思绪有点紊乱
you rest for a while
你先休息一会儿
I'll go get you medicine
我去给你备药
What's this
这是什么
tears
泪水
Little Lord
少主
Go get some medicine for Bai Ying
去给白璎准备一些药
White King wakes up
白王醒了
Will the king be all right when he wakes up?
白王醒了以后都还好吗
She needs to recover
她身体还需恢复
and
而且
and what
而且什么
She doesn't seem to know me fully
她似乎不完全认识我
don't know you fully
不完全认识你
What does it mean
这是什么意思
She knew me as the emperor of the sea
她认识我是海皇
But she doesn't know Su G
可她不认识苏摹
Possibly weak from a serious injury
也许是重伤初愈 身体虚弱
Mind is not yet clear
神志还没有完全清明
Yes
是
Let's wait until she recovers
等她恢复了再说吧
Lord, don't worry too much
少主你也不要太过担心
At least the white king has woken up
起码白王已经醒了
everything will be fine
一切都会好的
at least she woke up
是 至少她醒过来了
Little Lord
少主
Neptune
海皇
His Royal Highness asked me to come to take care of A Ying
太子殿下让我前来照顾阿璎
You will still be free
以后你还是自由的
you can go anywhere you want
你可以去任何你想去的地方
choose someone you love
选择一个你所爱的人
stay together forever
好好相守一生
Shark Izumi
泉先鲛人
You can only love one person in your life
一生一世只能爱一个人
A Yuan
阿鸢
have not seen you for a long time
好久不见
Long time no see, Jixiu
好久不见啊 治修
Aying how is she now
阿璎她现在如何
she just woke up
她刚刚醒
That's great
那太好了
I'm going to see her now
我现在就去见见她
Come with me
跟我来吧
Sister Hongyuan, you are here
红鸢姐 你来了
Fortunately, Su G has rescued you again.
还好苏摹又把你救醒了
You are trapped in Longyuan
你们在困龙渊
what exactly happened
究竟发生了什么事啊
saved me again
又救了我
Has he rescued me before?
他之前救过我吗
Do not you remember
你不记得了吗
I remember I went to Ruyi Casino
我记得我去如意赌坊
I went to find Na Sheng.
是去找那笙的
Do you remember Su G?
你还记得苏摹这个人吗
why do you ask
你为什么也这么问
did something happen
是发生了什么事吗
fine
没事
You just woke up and need to recover
你才刚醒过来还需要恢复
until you fully recover
等你完全恢复了
take it slow
再慢慢来吧
I'll go get you a glass of water
我去给你倒杯水
Have a good rest
先好好休息啊
Little Lord
少主
I'll deliver it later
待会儿再送吧
Yes
是
You two haven't seen each other in a hundred years.
你们俩百年没有再相见了
A hundred years ago
百年前一别
never seen again
再也没有见过
See you again in a hundred years
百年以后还能再相见
It's really fate
真的是缘分
ice cube brother
冰块哥哥
Ice cube brother, you are out of customs
冰块哥哥 你出关了
how are you feeling better
你怎么样 身体好些了吗
What about sister Bai Ying?
白璎姐姐呢
she woke up
她醒了
great great great
太好了太好了
That's right, ice cube
对了 冰块哥哥
What's wrong
怎么了
The news just came from Taoyuan County
刚刚桃源郡传来消息
I can go to save Yanxi.
可以去救炎汐了
message to you
消息传给你的
It was the news that Ning Liang received.
是宁凉收到的消息
Why didn't she tell me
她怎么没告诉我
you just closed
刚刚你在闭关
Ning Liang went to save Yan Xi first.
宁凉就先去救炎汐了
How can she go by herself
她怎么能自己去
Ning Liang is so awesome
宁凉那么厉害
And Xiang's help
还有湘的帮忙
I should be able to bring Yan Xi back smoothly.
应该可以把炎汐顺利接应回来吧
The young master received new news
少主 收到新的消息
It was a call for help from Xiang.
是湘发来的求救
Xiang
湘
Yan Xi and Ning Liang will not be in danger, right?
炎汐和宁凉不会有危险吧
Thank you for the medicine
谢谢你送的药
did not expect
没想到
we'll see you here
我们会在这里见到
a hundred years
一别百年
I thought we'd never see each other again
还以为永远都不会再相见了
Yes
是啊
Unpredictable
世事难料
A Yuan
阿鸢
You've had a hard time in the past hundred years, haven't you?
这百年你过得很辛苦吧
master
师父
master master
师父 师父
Our homework is done
我们的功课完成了
Master, this is
师父 这位是
This is Kong Sang's Red King Hongyuan
这位啊 是空桑的赤王红鸢
She came here on purpose to take care of the white king
她是特意来此处照顾白王的
red kite
红鸢
That name sounds familiar
这个名字有点耳熟啊
you know me
你们认识我
just heard
只是听过
Once master he
有一次师父他
Che's wounded Quanxian soldiers all return
澈 受伤的泉先士兵悉数归来
urgently needed medication
急需用药
Why don't you and Han go to the pharmacy to sort out the herbs?
你跟涵去药房整理药材吧
Yes
是
Once the master called him in a dream
有一次师父他梦里叫的
Looks like Ai
好像就是阿鸢
quick
快
How is this going
这是怎么回事
Ning Liang, take Yan Xi and go first
宁凉 你带着炎汐先走
I have already returned the sound transmission beads to the camp for help.
我已经传音珠回大营求救了
There should be someone on the way to pick you up
路上应该会有人来接应你们
I'm going back
我先回去了
good
好
can you go
走得了吗
Nanzhao
南昭
catch these people
抓住这些人
You go to my palace first
你们先走 我殿后
Abandoning comrades is not my Ning Liang style
抛弃战友不是我宁凉的风格
let's go together
我们一起走
quick
快
Ning Liang
宁凉
How about it
怎么样
Ning Liang is ineffective
宁凉办事不力
please punish
请少主责罚
You are alone
你一个人孤军奋战
It's not easy to hold on till now
撑到现在已经很不容易了
Don't waste your energy on me
不用浪费力气在我身上
I know I can't
我知道我不行了
can you please grant me a request
少主 可否答应我一个请求
You said
你说
after my death
在我死后
bury me in the sea
将我葬身大海
I want to stay where I started forever
我想永远留在最开始的地方
You are the soldiers of Quan Xianjun
你们就是泉先军的战士
martyrdom
如若殉义
Your blood will be written in your name
你们的鲜血将写就你们的名字
Always remembered by the ancestors of Dragon God and Izumi
被龙神和泉先子民永远记住
you will watch from heaven
你们会在天上看着
Quanxian returns to Biluohai
泉先回归碧落海
Ning Liang
宁凉
Ning Liang, don't worry
宁凉你放心
soon
很快
it's all over
这一切就会结束了
Please
请你
watch us from the sky
在天上看着我们
That is the place where Lord Haihuang cultivates and heals his wounds.
那是海皇大人修炼和疗伤的地方
right at the end of the hallway
就在走廊的尽头
Trespassers will be punished by the elders
擅闯者可是会被长老们惩罚的
someday
总有一天
this is mine
这是属于我的
A Ying
阿璎
what are you doing here
你在这里做什么
What is this place
这是什么地方
I do not know either
我也不知道
But let's not stay here
不过我们还是不要在这里逗留了
But I just saw
可是我刚刚看到
A man who looks like Su G entered
有一个长得好像苏摹的人进去了
No way
不会吧
Jixiu told me just now
刚才治修跟我说
He went to save Yanxi and the others
他去救炎汐他们了
he's not in the camp
他不在大营里
Am I wrong
难道我看错了
you just recovered
你才刚恢复
It's possible to be wrong
看错也是有可能的
what happened to Aying
阿璎 怎么了
fine
没事
You said they went to find Yanxi
你说他们去找炎汐了
Yan Xi was captured in the trapped Longyuan
炎汐在困龙渊被抓走了
Su G went to save him
苏摹去救他了
then let's go
那我们走吧
white king red king
白王 赤王
This is Neptune's ice room
这是海皇的冰室
Do not trespass without permission
未经允许 请勿擅闯
sorry we went the wrong way
抱歉 我们走错了
let's go
走吧
You're not dead yet with that sword of sleepy Longyuan
困龙渊那一剑你竟然还没死
Su G to save you
苏摹为了救你
Don't hesitate to let yourself suffer from backlash
不惜让自己承受反噬之苦
Even I suffer
连我都跟着受苦
Then you and Su G will die together
到时候你就和苏摹一起死吧
Brother ice cube has been gone for so long
冰块哥哥走了这么久
Why haven't you come back?
怎么还不回来啊
City injury
都怪我
I shouldn't have let Yu Huan take Yan Xi away
我不该让羽幻把炎汐带走的
Where was Yan Xi taken away by Yu Huan?
炎汐是在哪儿被羽幻带走的
Trapped in Longyuan
在困龙渊啊
you and brother ice cube were
你和冰块哥哥当时
Is to go to sleepy Longyuan to release the seal of the Dragon God
是要去困龙渊解龙神封印
Sister Bai Ying, you don't remember
白璎姐姐 你不记得了
I remember I went to Sleepy Longyuan
我记得我去了困龙渊
but other things
但是其他事情
I can't remember
我记不清了
fine
没事
You were so badly injured this time
你这次受了那么严重的伤
just right
也才刚好
It's normal not to remember
不记得也很正常
But I will never forget Yanxi
不过我是一定不会忘记炎汐的
My affair with Yanxi
我和炎汐的事情
remember clearly
都记得清清楚楚
He must come back safely
他一定要平安回来
they're back they're back
回来了 他们回来了
quick
快
Are they back?
是他们回来了吧
Sister Bai Ying
白璎姐姐
Let's go and see
走走走 咱们去看看
hurry up
快 走啊
hold onto
坚持住
Yanxi
炎汐
What about Yanxi?
炎汐呢
what happened to yanxi
炎汐怎么样了
It should be fine
应该没有大碍了
Take Ning Liang back to her room
把宁凉带回她的房间
Let Zhixiu check Yanxi's injury
让治修查看一下炎汐的伤势
Yes
是
Ning Liang she
宁凉她
I didn't protect everyone
是我没有保护好大家
how did you come out
你怎么出来了
Na Sheng is worried about Yan Xi
那笙担心炎汐
I'll accompany her here waiting for you to come back
我陪她在这里等你们回来
Are you OK
你没事吧
i'm fine
我没事
Just Hanzhou Ningliangting
只是寒洲 宁凉 汀
and others
还有其他人
They all fell one by one on the way home
都一个一个倒在了回家的路上
I sometimes think
我有时候就在想
If only I could be stronger
我要是能再强一点
will they be alright
是不是他们就会没事
Can you really take them home?
是不是就能真的带他们回家
back to blue sea
回到碧落海
Don't blame yourself too much
你不要太自责了
No one can save everyone
没有谁可以拯救所有的人
you don't take all the responsibility
你不要把所有的责任
carry it all on oneself
都扛在自己身上
never mind
没事了
go back and rest
回去休息吧
correct
对了
I saw someone enter the ice room today
我今天看到有人进了冰室
I thought it was you
我原本以为是你
But when I got in, there was no one there
可是进去以后发现空无一人
Did an outsider break into the Quanxian Camp?
难道有外人闯入了泉先大营
are you sure
你确定吗
Could it be that you are wrong?
会不会是你看错了
No, I can't read it wrong
没有啊 我不会看错
They said that no one dared to trespass in Quanxian's ice room
他们说泉先的冰室没有人敢擅闯
But I'm still a little worried
可是我还是有点不放心
Do not worry
不用担心
I'll find someone to find out
我会找人查清楚的
Maybe you are really wrong
或许真的是你看错了
is there anything else
还有什么事吗
Have I been to the ice room before?
我之前是不是来过冰室
what do you remember
你想起什么了
just feel a little familiar
只是觉得有一点熟悉
no matter what happens next
不论以后发生什么样的事情
I won't let you disappear again
我都不会再让你消失
I will always be with you
我都会一直陪着你
would you believe me
你愿意相信我吗
Forget it
先别想了
Maybe after the injury is healed
或许等伤好了以后
naturally remember
自然就会想起来
go back to rest early
早点回去休息吧
Yanxi
炎汐
Zhixiu said you're fine
治修说你并无大碍
But why can't you wake up?
但你为什么还醒不过来啊
you
你
Every time you go out, you come back hurt
每次你出去都是一身伤回来
I will follow you no matter what
以后不管什么事我都要跟着你
You can't get rid of me
你甩也甩不掉我
I don't want another time
我不想再有下一次了
I am so scared
我好怕
Those people are so vicious
那些沧流人好歹毒
How many more are they going to kill us?
他们到底还要害我们多少人
Your assignment is done
您交代的事办完了
Master Shi Peng, rest assured
师彭大人放心
I deliberately procrastinated
我故意拖延了时间
Wait until Su G appears
一直等到苏摹出现
rescued people from your hands
是从你的手中把人救走的
Yes
是
The Battle of Trapped Longyuan
困龙渊一战
Yuhuan's casualties were so heavy
羽幻伤亡如此惨重
But it didn't damage Su G half a point
却未损伤到苏摹半分
It seems that I abandoned Yuhuan this child
看来我弃羽幻这个子
It's not wrong to give up
弃得一点都不冤
Ah, you are awake
阿幻 你醒了
elder sister
姐姐
Where is Ah Huan feeling now?
阿幻 现在哪里不舒服吗
what's going on outside
外面什么情况
why am i here
我怎么在这儿啊
who saved me
到底是谁救的我
Fei Lian
是飞廉
Not only did he bring you back
他不只把你给带回来了
We also design together
我们还一起设计
Forcing Lord Shilang to send a medical officer to heal you
迫使师朗大人派医官来医治你
What about him now?
那他现在人呢
After Lord Shi Lang took him back
师朗大人把他带回去后
I have no further contact with him
我跟他就没有再联系了
What about the prisoner I caught, Yan Xi?
那我抓的那个犯人炎汐呢
Yan Xi was taken back to Mirror City
炎汐被带回镜城
Guarded by Master Shi Peng
由师彭大人看守
Quanxian should cooperate with the inside and outside
泉先里应外合
It was the Emperor of the Sea who came forward to rescue Yan Xi.
是海皇亲自出面救走炎汐的
The trapped Longyuan Cangliu Army suffered heavy losses this time.
此次困龙渊沧流军损失惨重
Yan Xi was rescued again
炎汐又被救走了
This time the fifth division has no reason
这回五师没有任何理由
leave me alone
可以放过我了
师彭 Adult
师彭大人
you are
您这是
Feather magic
羽幻
Battle of the Trapped Dragon Abyss
困龙渊之战
you as commander
你作为指挥官
Inflicted heavy damage to the Cangliu Legion
令沧流军团损伤惨重
If you want to deal with military law, you should be executed immediately
要按军法处置的话当立斩
but
不过
I have already helped you beg for mercy in front of the fourth division
我已经帮你在四师面前求过情
As long as you explain the reason for the defeat clearly
只要你把战败的原因交代清楚
I believe we will give you a fair deal
相信我们会给你个公正的处置
win
拿下
what do you do
你们做什么
sister is fine
姐姐 没事
you guys let him go
你们 你们放开他
Ah Huan
阿幻
How about it
怎么样
everything is alright here
你这边一切都好吧
Yanxi has returned
炎汐已经回来了
only
只是
Ning Liang died
宁凉殉义了
how so
怎么会这样
How about Taoyuan County?
桃源郡那边怎么样
as you might expect
正如你所料
With the cooperation of Gao Shunzhao
有了高舜昭的配合
Taoyuan County was easily taken down
桃源郡很轻松就拿下来了
Taoyuan County Commander Guo Yanyun
桃源郡总兵郭燕云
Received Governor's Secret Order
已收到总督密令
All the soldiers of Taoyuan County obey the orders of General Xijing
桃源郡全体士兵听令于西京将军
where did these two come from
这两个人从哪里冒出来的
who are they
他们是谁啊
Should the generals obey them?
总兵难道要听令于他们
I heard that Governor Gao has been stabbed
听闻高总督已被刺
Are they here to take the opportunity to capture Taoyuan County?
难道他们是来趁机夺取桃源郡的
Cangliu people will not give up
沧流人不会善罢甘休的
We will be the only casualties
到时候伤亡的只有我们
General Soldier
总兵大人
Taoyuan County soldiers swear to defend Taoyuan County
桃源郡士兵誓死守卫桃源郡
never surrender easily
绝不轻易投降
Two-headed Garuda Token
双头金翅鸟令牌
Holder's Order Towon-gun
持有者号令桃源郡
centuries
百年来
Cangliu people disturbed Taoyuan County
沧流人将桃源郡搅得民不聊生
A few months ago, it even sent the wind falcon
数月前更是派风隼
Burned Taoyuan County to the ground
将桃源郡烧得满目疮痍
As long as you are willing to submit to Kongsang
只要各位肯归顺于空桑
We will return Taoyuan County to peace
我们定当还桃源郡以安宁
people's well-being
百姓安康
It's time for yourself
是时候该为了自己
Defend Taoyuan County
守卫桃源郡
I am Guo Yanyun
我郭燕云
Willing to obey the command of Prince Yu Zhenlan, General Xijing
愿听令于真岚太子 西京将军
I hope everyone
我希望大家
able to unite
能够团结一心
share the same hatred
同仇敌忾
I am empty of thousands of soldiers
我空桑数千士兵
waiting outside the city gate
正在城门外等着
Waiting to guard the home with the soldiers
等着与将士们一起守卫家园
Restoring peace in Taoyuan County
还桃源郡安宁
I let Xijing stay in Taoyuan County
我让西京留在桃源郡
Deploy what's next
部署接下来的事情
Do not worry
你放心吧
correct
对了
What's wrong with Aying? Is she awake?
阿璎怎么样了 她醒了吗
she's awake
她已经醒过来了
woke up
醒了
That
那
can i go see her
那我能去看看她吗
sure
当然可以
Her injuries are no longer serious
她的伤势已无大碍
only
只是
just what
只是什么
Her memory is a little confused
她的记忆有些混乱
She only remembers me as a sea emperor
她只记得我是一个海皇
other things with her
跟她其他的事情
she doesn't even remember
她都不记得了
What about her to others?
那她对其他人呢
go and see
去看看再说吧
A Ying
阿璎
Your Highness
殿下
How are you doing?
怎么样 身体还好吗
I'm all right
我没事了
it's fine
没事就好
Did you come back from Taoyuan County?
你从桃源郡回来吗
Yes
是啊
Xijing and I joined forces to win Taoyuan County
我和西京合力拿下了桃源郡
He stayed there for a few days before coming back
他留在那里 过几日才回来
Your Highness
殿下
do you know what this is
你知道这是什么吗
This doesn't seem to be something we are empty of.
这好像不是我们空桑的东西
Why do I have such a thing
我为什么会有这样的东西啊
this
这个
try to recall the past
尝试回忆过往
Bai Ying, she will have a terrible headache
白璎她会头疼得厉害
Maybe forget your love with me
或许忘记与我的情意
She will live easier
她会活得更轻松些
Your Highness
殿下
A Ying
阿璎
you just recovered
你刚恢复好
Pay attention to your body
要注意身体
Don't think so much
就别想那么多了
Your Highness, I seem to
殿下 我好像
forgot something very important
忘了一些很重要的事情
what's the matter
什么事啊
I do not know either
我也不知道
But in my mind
可是我脑海中
It seems that the memory of the sea emperor is fuzzy
好像关于海皇的记忆都是模糊的
what happened between me and him
我跟他之间到底发生了什么事
Aying, the matter between you and Haihuang
阿璎 你和海皇的事情
I think you'd better ask him yourself
我想你还是亲自问他比较好
Aying, what do you need me to do?
阿璎 你有什么需要我做的
I'll do it for you
我去帮你做
Aying, I wish for a lot of things
阿璎 我希望过很多事
But not everything is perfect
可并不是事事都能圆满
I like you
我喜欢你
But I won't take advantage of others
但我不会趁人之危
But if you have a different choice
可是如果你有不同的选择
I don't want to let go easily
我也不想轻易放手
you woke up you really woke up
你醒了 你真的醒了
between me and him
我跟他之间
what happened
到底发生了什么事
Neptune
海皇
not sleeping so late
这么晚还不睡啊
I have been disturbed in Quanxian during this time.
这段时间在泉先多有打扰
thanks to you too
也多亏了你
My body can gradually recover
我的身体才能逐渐恢复
I have something to ask you
我有些事情想问你
You said
你说
i know i forgot something
我知道我忘记了一些事情
But these things should be about you
但这些事情应该跟你有关
Sister Hongyuan and His Royal Highness the Prince
红鸢姐姐还有太子殿下
They are all speechless
他们都欲言又止
So I had to ask you
所以我只好来问你
what happened to me
我是发生了什么吗
and
还有
Is this bead related to you?
这颗珠子是不是跟你有关
the things you can't remember
那些记不起来的事情
do you still care
你还在意吗
I've been trying to piece together
我一直在努力地去拼凑
memory left in mind
脑海中残存的记忆
But I can't remember
可是我怎么也想不起来
even if i tell you
就算我告诉你
That's just a story
那不过也是一个故事而已
Why are you obsessed with this?
你又何必执着于此呢
Maybe these memories are important to me
或许这些记忆对我来说很重要
doesn't it matter
难道不重要吗
As long as you live it's more important than anything
只要你能活着比什么事情都重要
I plan to leave the Quanxian camp tomorrow.
我明日打算离开泉先大营了